[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the epic movie Appaloosa, Viggo Mortensen displays considerable horseback riding skills. In what movie did he previously co-star with a wild mustang?", "correct_answer": "Hidalgo", "incorrect_answers": ["Carlitos Way", "A Perfect Murder", "The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical formula for baking soda?", "correct_answer": "NaHCO3", "incorrect_answers": ["Co3", "C3H8", "C12 H22 O11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What role did Terrance Howard play in the 1995 movie Dead Presidents?", "correct_answer": "Cowboy", "incorrect_answers": ["Cutty", "Dugan", "Nicky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the first symptoms of dental caries.  It is most pronounced when consuming sweet, hot or cold foods and liquids.", "correct_answer": "Toothache", "incorrect_answers": ["Numbness", "Bad breath", "Saliva overproduction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you see the characters \u201cS17\u201d printed on a Blackjack table what valuable information do you get about the rules of the game in this casino?", "correct_answer": "The dealer stands on soft 17s", "incorrect_answers": ["Soft 17s are considered eights by the dealer", "The dealer surrenders on soft 17s", "The dealer doubles on soft 17s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color lightsaber does Anakin Skywalker have?", "correct_answer": "Blue", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Purple", "Green"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What singer and actress performed the song Ill Be Seeing You at the 81st Academy Awards 2009 in memory of those who passed away since the previous years Academy Award ceremony?", "correct_answer": "Queen Latifah", "incorrect_answers": ["Mariah Carey", "Jennifer Hudson", "Beyonce"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular cocktail is made simply by mixing vodka and orange juice?", "correct_answer": "Screwdriver", "incorrect_answers": ["Colombia", "Wilson", "Madras"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Roger Allers took what part in the making of the Disney classic, The Lion King (1994).", "correct_answer": "Director", "incorrect_answers": ["He provided Simbas voice", "Script writer", "Cameraman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What mountain covers about 65% of the territory of Switzerland?", "correct_answer": "the Alps", "incorrect_answers": ["the Apennines", "the Andes", "Ararat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who hosted the 81st Academy Awards ceremony on February 22, 2009, at the Kodak Theatre in Los Angeles, California?", "correct_answer": "Hugh Jackman", "incorrect_answers": ["Jessica Biel", "Rupert Everett", "Ellen DeGeneres"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Venus is named after the Roman Goddess of what?", "correct_answer": "Love", "incorrect_answers": ["Truth", "Lust", "Beauty"]}]